Dustin Raimondi

Media Developer

dustin.raimondi.rocks

raimondi1337@gmail.com

I am a recent graduate from Rochester Institute of Technology. I have experience with application development on web, mobile, Windows and Linux, and I have a strong sense for User Experience. My current strengths are NodeJS front-end frameworks such as React and Backbone, and data visualization. In my spare time I ride work on my motorcycle and travel.

Education

Rochester Institute of Technology - Rochester, NY

2011 - 2016

Bachelor of Science in New Media Interactive Development in the Golisano College of Computing and Information Sciences

Experience

Datto Inc. - Norwalk, CT

January 2015 - June 2015

Software Engineering Internship

Front-end web development with Backbone and internal projects with

RIT Office of Development and Alumni Relations

June 2014 - August 2014

Technical Strategist

Assessment, research and implementation of solutions for varied special projects

RIT College Activities Board

January 2013 - November 2014

Technology Coordinator

Website design, development and maintenance, system administration, technology appropriation and network administration

My Buzzwords

Front End Web Development Node, Grunt, React, Backbone

User Experience Interface Design, Data Visualization

Project Management Agile, Scrum, Git, Slack

Server Configuration Apache, Nginx, Linode

Free Open Source Software Python and Licensing

Database Implementation MySQL, Oracle, Mongo, Redis

Mobile Development Java, XML, Objective C, C

Adobe Creative Suite Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere